Lewes
Did we really make ten million
It feels like a dream
why did you pinch me
If it hurts, it's not a dream
Our Lewes really made ten million
Mom, Dad
Cynthia
This isn't a dream
Our family is really rich now
I was thinking
we should renovate our old house
You've worked hard most of your lives
It's time you enjoyed yourselves
Okay
My son has finally made it
We'll listen to you
We'll do whatever you say
It's so beautiful
I
can live in such a nice house in my lifetime
I owe it all to you
Our old rundown house
leaked everywhere when it rained
I never dreamed
we'd live in a house like this
The hard days are over
From now on, you and Dad
can just relax and enjoy life
Mom, Dad
Cynthia
Let's go
Let's take a look